eachbuyer.com 2013-09-26

# Privacy Policy

[EachBuyer.com only asks for specific types of personal information](http://www.1topstore.com/Privacy_policy.php#2)  
[EachBuyer.com ](http://www.1topstore.com/Privacy_policy.php#2)[ will not disclose your personal information to any outside organization for its use in marketing without your consent](http://www.1topstore.com/Privacy_policy.php#4)  
[You can opt-out of 1topstore.com’s marketing list at any time](http://www.1topstore.com/Privacy_policy.php#6)  

**Privacy and Data Security**

At www.eachbuyer.com, your right of privacy and data security is a primary concern. That’s why, when you visit www.eachbuyer.com, we help you maintain control over your personal data on the Internet.   
At any time you may contact www.eachbuyer.com with any privacy questions or concerns you may have. You also may ask at any time to see the personal data you have given us and request correction or deletion. We strive to protect the security of your personal data by use of appropriate measures and processes. Below are the guidelines we use for protecting the information you provide us during a visit to our Internet site or when you use our online support offerings such as FAQ at www.eachbuyer.com.

**www.eachbuyer.com  only asks for specific types of personal information**

In a few areas on our Web site and online customer support tools, we ask you to provide information that will enable us to enhance your site visit, to assist you with purchase and technical support issues or to follow up with you after your visit. It is completely optional for you to participate.   
1\. For example, we request information from you when you: Register on www.eachbuyer.com    
2\. Request a quote   
3\. Place an order   
4\. Request e-mail notification of your order status   
5\. Subscribe to a newsletter or a mailing list   
Information we may request includes your name, e-mail address, phone number, address, company name, customer preference information, customer number and order number, as well as other similar personal information. If we ever ask for significantly different information we will inform you.

**www.eachbuyer.com  only uses your personal information for specific purposes**

The information you provide will be kept confidential and used to support your customer relationship with www.eachbuyer.com. Among other things, we want to help you quickly find information on www.eachbuyer.com and alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new products and services from www.eachbuyer.com. Agents or contractors of www.eachbuyer.com who have access to your personal information and prospect information are required to keep the information confidential and not use it for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for www.eachbuyer.com. www.eachbuyer.com may enhance or merge your information collected at its site with data from third parties for purposes of marketing products or services to you.

In addition, www.eachbuyer.com may be required to disclose personal information in connection with law enforcement, fraud prevention, regulation, and other legal action or if www.eachbuyer.com reasonably believes it is necessary to do so to protect www.eachbuyer.com, its customers, or the public.

**www.eachbuyer.com  will not disclose your personal information to any outside organization for its use in marketing without your consent**

Information regarding you (such as name, address and phone number) or your order and the products you purchase will not be given or sold to any outside organization for its use in marketing or solicitation without your consent. Your information may be shared with agents or contractors of www.eachbuyer.com for the purpose of performing services for www.eachbuyer.com.

**Internet Commerce**

The online store at www.eachbuyer.com is designed to give you options concerning the privacy of your name, address, e-mail and any other information you provide us. www.eachbuyer.com is committed to data security with respect to information collected on our site. We offer the industry standard security measures available through your browser called SSL encryption, at our payment gateways. It has always been an www.eachbuyer.com practice to contact customers in the event of a potential problem with your purchase or any normal business communication regarding your purchase.

**You can opt-out of  www.eachbuyer.com’s marketing list at any time**

Periodically, we may send you information about our various products and services, or other products and services we feel may be of interest to you. Only www.eachbuyer.com (or agents working on behalf of www.eachbuyer.com s and under confidentiality agreements) will send you these direct mailings. If you do not want to be included on www.eachbuyer.com’s marketing list, simply tell us when you give us your personal information. Or, at any time you can easily opt-out of www.eachbuyer.com’s marketing list or update your information by logging in your personal account.

**Customized Experience**

We use technology to help us deliver customized visitor experiences. At www.eachbuyer.com, we primarily use "cookies" to help us determine which service and support information is appropriate to your machine and to maintain your shopping experience in our online store. Our use of this technology does not mean that we automatically know any information about you. We might be able to ascertain what type of computer you are using, but beyond that, our use of cookies is designed only to provide you with a better experience when using www.eachbuyer.com. www.eachbuyer.comhas no desire or intent to infringe on your privacy while using the www.eachbuyer.com site.

**Third-Party Sites**

Please be aware that other web sites that may be accessed through our site may collect personally identifiable information about you. The information practices of those third-party web sites linked to www.eachbuyer.com are not covered by this privacy statement.

You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you’re online. If you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. While we strive to protect your personal information, www.eachbuyer.comcannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

**Other Web sites**

www.eachbuyer.com’s Web site contains links to other Web sites that are not operated by www.eachbuyer.com. www.eachbuyer.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of the Web sites that it does not operate. Some parts of the Web site are animated using various downloadable applications, such as Macromedia’s Shockwave/Flash.
